[
    {
        "front": "width and height",
        "back": "<p>(box model) width</p><ul>    <li>distance from left inner edge to right iner edge height</li>    <li>inner top edge to inner bottom edge</li></ul><p>note: this properties do not apply to inline non-replace elements</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "margin",
        "back": "<p><strong>margin</strong> -&nbsp;<span style=\"line-height:1.6em\">separation between most normal-flow elements occurs because of margins.&nbsp;</span></p><p>h1 {margin: 0.25in; background-color: silver;}</p><p>- sets a quarter inch of blank space around an h1 element</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "margin eamples",
        "back": "<p>(margin: top right bottom left - TRBL &#39;trouble&#39;)</p><p>h1 {margin: 10px 20px 15px 5px;}</p><p>h1 {margin: 10px 20px;} /* equivalent&nbsp;h1 {margin: 10px 20px 10px 20px;} */</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "margins and inline elements",
        "back": "<p>applying margins to an inline nonreplaced element will have no effect on the line-height,&nbsp;<span style=\"line-height:1.6em\">only the left and right margins are effected</span></p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "border",
        "back": "<p><strong>border</strong> - simply one or more lines that surround the content and padding of an element.</p><p>Three attributes: width, style, color.</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "border-style examples",
        "back": "<p>a:link {border-style: outset;}</p><p>p.aside {border-style: solid dashed dotted solid;}</p><p>h1 {border-style:solid; border-left-style: none;}</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "border-width examples",
        "back": "<p>p { border-width: thick; }</p><p>h1 {border-style: dotted; border-width: thin 0;}</p><p>p {border-style: solid; border-width: 15px 2px 7px 4px;}</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "border-color",
        "back": "<p>p {border-style: solid; border-color: gray;}</p><p>h1 {border-style: solid; border-color: black rgb(25%,25%,25%,25%) #808080 silver;}</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "shorthand border properties",
        "back": "<p>h1 {border-bottom: thick solid gray;}</p><p>h2 {border: thick silver solid; border-left-width: 20px;}</p>"
    },
    {
        "front": "padding",
        "back": "<p>h1 {padding: 10px; background-color:silver;}</p><p>h2 {padding: 0.5em 2em;}</p><p>h3 {padding-left: 0.25in;}</p>"
    }
]
